我要点咖啡外带
I'm gonna get some more coffee to go.
洋娃娃  你也要吗
Do you want anything more baby-doll?
不用了  谢谢
I'm fine, thanks.
我不能叫你洋娃娃吧
Yeah, see, I can't pull off baby-doll can I?
不行  从甜甜嘴事件我们已经学到教训了
No. I think we learned that from the sugarlips incident.
-我去点茶来喝  -好
- I'm gonna get some tea. - Okay.
-小亲亲  你好吗  -不准叫
- Hiya doin' pumpkin? - Nope.
你们俩真是越来越甜蜜了呢
So it looks like it's going really well for you two, huh?
的确是很好
I know, really well.
其实我正想邀菲比和我同居
In fact, I'm gonna ask Phoebe to move in with me.
我的天
Oh my God!
你觉得呢
What do you, what do you think?
我觉得这真是太棒了  你什么时候问她
I think that is so great! When are you gonna ask her?
今天晚上  你先别透露哦
Tonight, but don't say anything. Okay?
我发誓不说  我保证
I swear, I promise. I promise.
天啊  我好激动
Oh my God, I'm so excited!
我跟你说  记得不要送花给她
All right, listen let me tell you, do not get her flowers. Okay?
因为花谢了她会哭
Because y'know, she cries when they die,
还会帮花办葬礼之类的
and there's the whole funeral...
亲爱的  下班后见
I'll see you after work sweetie.
好  再见
Okay. Bye!
我们应该去看什么电影
So, what movie should we see?
盖瑞要请你搬去跟他住
Gary's gonna ask you to move in with him!!
什么  真的吗
What?! Really?!
他刚才在吧台告诉我的
He just told me at the counter.
他要我保证不说出去  但我实在是憋不住了
He made me promise not to tell, but I couldn't hold it in any longer!
我不敢相信
I can't believe this!
对  因为太快了  太快太快了
Right, because it's fast. Because, it's so fast. It's fast!
别激动  是菲比  又不是你
Relax! It's Phoebe! Not you!
菲比  很厉害  有一套
Oh! Good for you Pheebs, way to go!
不过真的是太快了  不是吗
No, but it is fast. Isn't it?
不会
No.
我是很喜欢他  但我还没准备好要同居
I like him a lot but I don't think I'm ready for this!
那你打算怎么办
So, what are you gonna do?
不知道  兵来将挡  干脆你去跟他谈
I don't know. I'll just handle it-I'll ask you to talk to him!
我  为何是我
Me?! Why me?
因为你怕死了给承诺
Because you are so afraid of commitment!
你去跟他说说  让他跟你一样怕
You talk to him, make him scared like you!
让他成为一个男人
Make him a...man!
我会去试试  但我不确定会多有用
I'll try, but I'm not sure what good it would do, y'know?
因为比起以前
Because I'm a lot less afraid
我现在已经没那么害怕承诺了
of commitment than I used to be.
我好感动
That is so sweet!
还是很怕  我会搞定的  没问题
Still terrified, I'll take care of it. No problem.
罗斯  斯塔滕岛真的是岛吗
Hey Ross, is uh, is Staten Island really an island?
是啊  所以才叫斯塔滕"岛"
Uh-huh, that's why they call it Staten Island.
我还以为跟长岛一样不是岛呢
Ohhh. I thought it was like Long Island.
长岛也是岛
Also an island.
几点了
Hey, what time is it?
2点17分
2:17.
你知道吗  我们丢这个球连续一小时
Wow! You realize that we've been throwing this ball,
都没有漏接落地
without dropping it, for like an hour?
真的吗
Are you serious?!
对  我半小时前就发现了
Yeah. I realized it about a half-hour ago
我怕坏了好事才没说
but I didn't want to say anything 'cause I didn't want to jinx it.
我们还真会丢接球呢
Wow! We are pretty good at this!
我们完全忘了吃午餐
Hey! We totally forgot about lunch!
这是我第一次忘记吃饭
Oh, I-I, I think that's the first time I ever missed a meal!
我的裤子都有点松了
Yeah, my pants are a little loose!
嗨  两位
Hey, you guys...
莫妮卡在吗
Is Monica here?
不在
No.
好的  听我说
All right listen umm,
我买了样东西  不确定她会不会喜欢
I just bought something I'm not sure she's gonna like it,
看起来可能有些疯狂
and it's gonna seem a little crazy,
但这是我从小就想要的
but this is something that I wanted since I was a little girl.
你买了肖恩·卡西迪(演艺界才子)
You bought Shawn Cassidy!
不是  我也想啊  你们准备好没
Noo! I wish! Okay, you ready?
好了
Yeah!
请看
Check it out!
那是什么啊
What-what is it?!
什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?!!
这是猫啊
It's a, it's a cat!
这才不是猫呢
That, is not a cat!
这就是猫啊
Yes it is!
它的皮怎么反了
Why is it inside out?!
拜托  这可是纯种的
Excuse me! But this is a purebred,
观赏级狮身人面猫
show-quality Sphinx cat!
你花了多少钱买的
How much did you pay for that?
有点奢侈  但价钱还算公道
Well, it was a little extravagant, but I got a pretty good deal.
是吗  多少钱
Yeah? How much?
一千块
A thousand bucks.
买一只猫
On a cat?!
那不是猫
It's not a cat!
玩球小子  给我听好了
All right listen ball boys!
我小时候奶奶就养了这种猫
My grandmother had one of these when I was a little girl
它们最讨人喜欢了
and it was the sweetest thing!
超可爱的
I mean it was so cute,
躺在我的膝盖上整天满足地喵喵叫
it would sit in my lap and purr all day long,
我还会拿鞋带在地上拖  让它追着跑
and I would drag a shoestring on the ground and he would chase it!
不要钱的猫也会那样
Free cats do that too, y'know.
那不是猫
It's not a cat!
反正我开心得不得了
Look you guys, I'm really excited about this! Okay?
我才不管你们怎么想
I don't care what you think!
我要去帮威丝克森太太张罗一个小猫砂盒
I'm gonna go set up a little litter box for Mrs. Whiskerson.
不然我要叫它什么  毛毛吗
Well, what am I gonna call her? Fluffy?!
你要去吃点东西吗
Hey, you wanna get something to eat
还是要看我们
or uh, do you wanna see how long
能来回丢多久
we can throw this ball back and forth? Huh?
继续丢球
Uhh, the ball thing.
是嘛
Yeah?
罗斯  如果我们能
Hey Ross, wouldn't it be great
连丢两小时球不落地  那样是不是很棒
if we could go two straight hours without dropping it?!
当然  来吧
Yeah it would! Let's do it!
好的
Okay!
不好
Uh-oh.
怎么了
What?
我要尿尿  瑞秋却在厕所里
I have to pee. And Rachel's in the bathroom!
没想到这样也行
Man, I didn't think we were gonna make it!
是啊  你别换手哦
I know!  Don't switch hands, okay?
小姐们  你们在这里干嘛
Hey ladies! What are you in here for?
钱德勒  你来这里干嘛
Hey Chandler, what are you doing here?
盖瑞  我是来报案的
Gary, I'm here to report a crime.
是吗
Yeah?
我们俩不常聚在一起是一种犯罪
It is a crime that you and I don't spend more time together.
你有什么事
What's up?
听说你在考虑
Well, I heard that you thinking about
邀菲比跟你同居  我心想
asking Phoebe to move in with you and I thought
我们或许应该聊聊
maybe, we should have a talk.
男人跟...我的对话
Man to uh, me.
好啊  没问题
Sure. Okay.
你疯了吗
Uh, are you crazy?
你在发什么神经
Are you insane?
如果你和菲比同居
If you live with Phoebe,
你们两个就会住在一起了
you two are gonna be y'know, live-living together!
对  我考虑过了
Yeah, I-I considered that.
我知道这会让我快乐
I just know it would make me happy.
你是说害怕吧
You mean scared.
不  我是说快乐
No, I mean happy.
害怕的快乐
Scared happy?
钱德勒  你在干嘛
Chandler, what-what are you doing?
我在帮你认清事实啊  兄弟
I am trying to open your eyes, my man!
你没意识到吗
Don't you see,
如果你和菲比同居  她就会永远在你眼前
if you lived with Phoebe she's always gonna be there.
你回家后  她在
You're gonna get home, she's there.
你上床睡觉  她在
You go to bed, she's there.
你起床后呢  对  她还是在
You wake up and oh yes, she's there!
我知道  我都等不及了
I know! I can't wait!
你父母的婚姻很幸福是吧
Were your parents happy, or something?
钱德勒  我看到的是
Listen Chandler, the way I see it is that
我很幸运能找到我的真爱
I was lucky enough to find someone that I really love.
我想要尽量多跟她在一起
I just-I wanna be around her as much as I can.
怪了  这事你说出来感觉就没那么恐怖了
Wow, y'know when you say it, it doesn't sound so scary.
你懂我的意思吧
See you know what I'm talking about, right?
对  我想我懂
Yeah, I think I do!
知道吗  你要和她一起住
Y'know what? You move in with her!
马上就去跟她同居
You move in with her right now!
或许我也应该和莫妮卡同居
Maybe I should in with Monica!
不成  你们不能操之过及
No, it's too soon for you guys.
是啊  你说的对
Yeah, you're right about that.
他们找到中生代乳齿象遗迹
...now when they found the remains of the Mesozoic Mastodon
却在颚部发现了
they discovered what appeared to be the remains
古生代两栖类的遗迹
of a Paleozoic Amphibian in its jaws!
那是怎么跑到它嘴里的
How did it get there?!
或许这个游戏应该安静一点
Maybe this should be more of a quiet game.
嗨
Hey guys!
Hi!
乔伊  我昨晚把手表放桌子上了
Joey, I left my watch on the counter last night.
就在这里  到哪儿去了
It was right here, where is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
别闹了  我上班快迟到了
All right, come on, I'm-I'm late for work!
你怎么知道  你又没戴表
How do you know? You don't have a watch.
兄弟们  能不能停一下再丢球
Guys, could you please just stop throwing the ball for one minute
先帮我找表
and just help me find it!
不知道  不行哦
Oh, I don't know.... Yeah, can't do it.
怎样啦
What?!
莫妮卡  怎样都好  千万别把球掉地上
Monica, whatever you do, do not drop that ball!
我们保持球不落地已经
Yeah, we haven't dropped it in...
2小时27分钟了
2 hours, 27 minutes.
是嘛
Really?!
我今天没办法去上班
I-I'm not gonna be able to make it into work today,
我不太舒服
I don't feel very good.
好的
Yes!!
我刚才突然
Wow! Uh, for a second there
觉得自己好多了  但其实没有
I thought I was really better, but I'm not.
瑞秋
Hey Rach!
快来看  球不落地接近三小时了
Check it out! Almost 3 hours without droppin' it!
恭喜了  真是浪费时间的好办法
Oh, wow! Congratulations, that's quite a waste of time.
-瑞秋  -怎么了
- Rach? - Yeah?
你身上都是抓痕  怎么了
You have scratches all over you, what happened?
是我的猫
Well, it's my cat.
什么
What?!
对了  我养了一只猫
Oh yeah, I got a cat.
我不想养猫
I don't want a cat!
别担心  那不是猫
Oh, don't worry, it's not a cat.
没错
Yeah.
这只猫跟我奶奶养过的猫完全不一样
You guys this cat is nothing like my grandmother's cat.
既不讨人喜欢  也不可爱
I mean, it's not sweet, it's not cute,
我在地上拉着线逗它玩
I even dragged that little string on the ground,
它竟然发飙  把我抓得乱七八糟
and it just flipped out and scratched the hell out of me.
我知道这听来很疯狂  但我发誓
And I swear, I know this sounds crazy,
这只猫每次冲我发出嘶嘶声
but every time this cat hisses at me
我知道它都在说"瑞秋"
I know it's saying, "Rachel!"
不及花一千块买一只猫疯狂
Doesn't sound as crazy as paying a thousand dollars for a cat.
你欠我三百块不还  还拿一千块去买猫
What?! You paid a thousand dollars for a cat when you owe me 300!!
我本来打算让你跟它玩的
Well, I was gonna let you play with it.
你跟盖瑞聊过同居的事没
Hmm, did you talk to Gary about the moving in thing?
聊过了  我觉得你应该答应
Yes I did, and I think you should do it.
什么
What?!
他很棒
He's a great guy, y'know?
他也很爱你  你非常幸运
And he loves you a lot, you are a very lucky lady.
你真没用
You are useless!
害怕承诺是你唯一会做的事
Freaking out about commitment is the one thing you can do!
你连唯一会做的都做不好  天啊
The one thing! And you can't even do that right! God!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
换作我都愿意和他同居
If you ask me, I'd move in with him.
天啊  你滚吧  没用鬼
God! Ooh! Get out of here, good for nothing.
钱德勒
Hey Chandler.
小盖
Hey Gar!
亲爱的
Hi sweetie.
-能不能先聊一下  -好啊
- Hi, can I talk to you for a second? - Yeah! Okay.
你今天很美
You look very pretty today.
谢谢
Thanks! Okay.
是这样的
Here's the thing.
我很想让这段关系更进一步
Y'know I really want to move this relationship forward.
因为  不更进一步
Because if you're not moving forward, y'know
就会不进则退
you're just moving backwards.
不对
No that's not true.
如果不进  就是静止不动
If you're not moving forward, you're just staying still.
静止不动是很好的  你看
And staying still is good. Watch this.
菲比  我要你搬来和我一起住
Phoebe, I want you to move in with me.
你好贴心
That is so sweet.
但你不觉得太快了些吗
But don't you think it's a little too soon?
我们彼此还有太多地方不了解
I mean there's so much we don't know about each other.
好吧  我懂了
Oh. Oh-oh-okay, I get it.
我只是不希望我们操之过急
I just-I don't want us to jump into something we're not ready for.
我不想搞砸我们现在所拥有的
I really don't want to mess up what we have.
我只是担心同居会铸成大错
I'm just-I'm worried it's gonna be a big mistake.
所以我的答案是我答应
Which is why my answer is yes!
真的吗
Really?!
是啊  我好快乐
Uh-huh! I'm so...happy.
莫妮卡  别丢那么大力
Monica! Stop throwing it so hard!
我们是同一队的
We're on the same team!
四个小时  你们就这样丢了四个小时
Four hours? You guys have been doing this for four hours?
宝贝  没错
That's right baby.
好  让我加入
All right, let me in.
不行  不行
No-no! Don't do it! Don't!
什么
What?
他是手滑大王
He's a dropper!
对  没错
Oh yeah, that's right!
我才不是手滑大王
I'm not a dropper!
这其实是三个人的游戏
It's really a uh-uh three person game, y'know?
还不就是你丢我接
It's throwing and catching!
好吧
All right.
好大力哦
Oh! Oh! That's so hard.
别紧张  那不是猫
Whoa-whoa you guys, it's not a cat!
我的天啊
Oh my-Oh good God!
我放弃了  我不知道要怎么处理
I give up you guys, I don't know what I'm going to do with this thing!
送它进烤箱也没用吗
Baking it didn't help, huh?
把它送回你买的地方呢
So, why don't you just take it back to where you got it?
我试过了  他们不收
I tried! They won't take her back.
或许是因为它是反基督的爪牙
Maybe that's because she's a minion of the anti-Christ.
瑞秋  店家为什么不收
Rach, why won't they take it back?
他们说要收回可以  但只退我店里的购物券
Well, they said would but they would only give me store credit.
我要拿来买什么  一千只普通的猫不成
I mean, what am I going to do, get a thousand regular cats?
那就先留在家里
Look, if you want you can keep it at our place
直到你找到处理的方法
until you find out what to do with it.
莫妮卡  那不是重点  我破费一千块
No Mon that's not the point. I'm out a thousand dollars,
搞得全身都是抓痕
I'm all scratched up,
还跟长得像手的蠢猫困在一起
and I'm stuck with this stupid cat that looks like a hand!
天啊  那只猫害我流眼泪了
Oh my God, the cat's made my eyes water!
别丢球给我
Don't-don't throw it to me!
我的视力受损
My vision's been compromised!!
天啊  好了  现在好了
Oh God! Okay. Okay. It's okay.
刚才好险
Man, that was close.
是啊  你差点就反应太大了
Yeah, you almost overreacted to something.
我们有个好消息
We have great news!
我们要同居了  是不是很棒
We're moving in together! Isn't it great! Yay!
恭喜
Congratulations! Congrats!
是啊  我好激动
I know, I'm so excited!
我也是
So am I!
你才没有我激动
Well, you're not more excited than I am!
不可能  我是最激动的
No way! I'm the most excited!
好  晚点在局里见
Okay, I'll see you at the station later.
好  晚点见  别忘了同居的事哦
Okay, yeah, I'll see you later! Don't forget about the moving in!
你要搬去跟他住  怎么了
So you're moving in with him. What happened?
看他伤心成那样  我不忍心拒绝他
I couldn't tell him no. He got so sad.
或许这样挺好
Maybe it'll be all right.
我真的很喜欢他
I do really like him a lot
同居八成也是迟早的事
and probably do it eventually anyway
想想也可以省下不少邮票钱
and plus, think of all the money I'll save on stamps.
怎么着  你常写信给他
Why, do you write him a lot?
不是  只是我听说同居的人
No, I just heard when people live together,
会分担邮票的费用  不是吗
they split the cost of stamps. Don't they?
-是啊  -没错
- Yeah! That's right. - Yeah-yeah! Yeah!
抱歉  隔热手套吓了我一跳
Oh, I'm sorry, the oven mitts really freaked me out.
亲爱的
Hey, honey!
你找到公寓没  布鲁克林高地有吗
Okay, so did you find any apartments? Anything in Brooklyn Heights?
不  没找到
No, nothing.
-真的  -是啊
- Oh really? - Yeah.
一间都没有
Nothing at all?
没有  只要有公寓招租  我们马上搬进去
No, as soon as something opens up we'll move right in.
不过要有泳池的  我需要泳池
Unless it doesn't have a pool, I need a pool.
菲比  可以跟你聊一下吗
Phoebe, can I talk to you for a second?
坐吧
Take a seat.
你没事吧  还好吗
You okay? You feeling all right?
我很好啊  因为我们要同居了
Yeah, I feel great. 'Cause we're moving in together.
这么说
So you uh,
报上布鲁克林高地的租屋广告  你都看过了
you checked the paper for listings in Brooklyn Heights, right?
邮报你有查过吗
You-you checked the Post?
有啊  什么都没有
Yeah, uh-huh, there was nothing.
我能喝点水吗
Can I get some water?
等一下
In a minute.
你查过今天的邮报吗
You-you checked today's Post?
对  今天的
Umm, yeah! Today's.
这是今天的邮报
'Cause uh, this is today's Post
我找到了这些租屋广告
and uh, these are the listings I found.
布鲁克林高地  两房
Brooklyn Heights, two bedroom.
布鲁克林高地  一房
Brooklyn Heights, one bedroom.
全是布鲁克林高地
Brooklyn Heights,  Brooklyn Heights,  Brooklyn Heights!
这些是要出租的吗
Are these for rent!
我以为他们是在炫耀自己的房子有多棒
I thought people were just bragging!
我来告诉你我的想法
Let me tell you what I think might be going on.
不要看桌子  看着我
No-no-no, don't look at the table. Look at me.
我认为一个男生邀请一个女生同居
Okay, I think somebody asked someone to move in with them.
女生本来说好  现在反悔了
And I think someone said, "Yes" but now she's having doubts
因为女生觉得这样太快了
because things are moving to fast for someone.
你觉得是不是这样
Does that sound at all possible to you?
对  好  我就是那个女生
Yes. Yes! Fine! I am someone!
你要我说老实话  我是不确定
You want me to say it? I have doubts!
对不起
I'm sorry!
菲比
Phoebe.
菲比  你有这种感觉也没关系
Phoebe, it's okay that you feel this way.
这真的是很快
I mean it is soon.
我们对彼此还有许多地方不了解
And there's a lot of things we don't know about each other,
我只是觉得
and I just figure that
我知道的你  我都很喜欢
everything I know about you I really like.
我还不知道的  就等同居后
And the things I don't know, I get to learn about at someplace
再慢慢了解
with both our names on the mailbox.
那样好甜蜜哦
That's so sweet.
亲爱的  但这些都不重要
Sweethart, but none of that matters
如果你觉得太快
if it's too soon for you.
没关系的  我们不用现在就同居
It's fine! We don't have to move in together.
我只要你快乐
I just-I want you to be happy.
跟你同居会让我快乐的
Living with you would make me happy.
菲比  你不用这样说
Phoebe, you don't have to say that.
不  我很想跟你住在一起  我要跟你同居
No, I really wanna live with you! I wanna move in with you!
你确定吗
Are you sure?
对  百分之百确定
Yes. Definitely! Yes!
我们一起住间公寓同居吧
Let's live in an apartment that we both live in!
太好了
Oh that's great!
等等
Oh wait, one sec. One sec.
镜子后面的人  你看个什么劲啊
Hey you! Behind the glass! Who are you looking at!
我每次进来这种房间
I've always wanted to say that everytime
都想说这句话  虽然我从没进来过
when I was in one of these rooms, which was never!
观赏猫  优质观赏猫
Show cat! Quality show cat!
观赏猫
Show cat!
天啊  你的宝宝怎么了
Oh my God! What's wrong with your baby?!
这不是宝宝  这是猫
It's not a baby! It's a cat!
长得还真吓人
Eew! It's creepy looking!
不会  它其实很讨人喜欢的
Oh no! No! It's actually-it's very sweet.
非常讨人喜欢  不信你看
It's very sweet. Look!
你要不要
Yeah, do you want it?
不  我讨厌猫
No, I hate cats.
那你干嘛跟我扯半天
Well, so then what are you doing to me? Okay?
走吧  继续走你的路
Just get out of here! All right? Move on!
真是的
Geez.
这只猫真不寻常
Wow! What an unusual cat!
是的  谢谢  正是这样  你要吗
Yes! Thank you! Exactly! You want it?
有可能  我正考虑要养猫
Maybe. I was thinking about getting a cat,
我正好要去流浪动物之家
I was just going to go to the shelter but...
好吧  就它了
Okay, why not?
太好了  总共是两千块
Oh, terrific! That'll be $2,000.
什么
What?!
好吧  一千
Okay, a thousand.
我以为你是要我认养你的猫
I thought you wanted to adopt your cat.
是啊  不过这不只是猫
Well, I do, but you're just gonna have to actually look at this
更是一项投资
as more of an investment than a cat.
好吧  我要的只是猫
Okay, yeah, I just wanted a cat.
你显然是砍价高手
Obviously you know how to haggle,
所以我就不唬弄你了
so I'm not gonna try and take you on. Okay?
算你八百  我也不报警了
So $800 and I don't call the cops which I should
因为你这根本是在抢劫
because you're robbing me blind! Blind!
把钱留下猫带走  溜之大吉吧  可恶
Just take cat, leave the money, and run away! Run away!  Damn it!
死猫  你起码也笑一下嘛
Cat, can't you at least smile or something?!
有没有人听到  谁听到了
Okay, did anybody just hear that? Anybody?
我饿死了
I'm starving!
你们振作一点
Come on guys! Suck it up!
就快达到连续十小时了  这是比毅力的时刻
We're closing in on ten hours! It's gut-check time!
怎么变成你当老大了
I don't know who made you the boss? All right?
这游戏是我们发明的
We invented this game!
拜托  这游戏是因为我才有现在的局面
Please! I made this game what it is.
不再好玩的局面吗
Not fun anymore?
我还是很饿
I'm still hungry!
好吧  我家还有一点比萨
All right, there's some pizza at my place,
你们可以用一只手吃吧  要不要
we can all eat with one hand right? Are you with me?
我要
I am!
好  我们走  来吧
All right! Let's go! Come on, come on.
莫妮卡大队  出发了
Let's go Team Monica!
好啦  队名等一下再讨论
All right, we can work out the name later.
瑞秋  你的猫在我碗里干嘛
Rachel! What is your cat doing in one of my bowls!
不是啦  我在解冻鸡肉
It's not! I'm defrosting a chicken.
我把威丝克森太太卖掉了
Oh, I sold Mrs. Whiskerson.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God!
你的钱拿回来没
Did you get your money back?
有  一千五百块
Yeah, 15 hundred dollars.
哇  你还有赚耶
Wow! You made a profit!
我是来拿红天鹅绒枕头的
I just came for the red-velvet pillow.
好的  给你
Oh yeah, there you go.
谢了  瑞秋
Thanks Rachel.
别忘了  你随时可以来看它
And-and don't forget you-you can come visit her anytime you want.
好的  我会记得的
Oh good, great! I'll-I'll keep that in mind.
这是什么  某种蛇吗
Hey! So what is this? Some kind of snake or something?
我真喜欢和你一起醒来
I really like waking up with you.
我也喜欢和你一起醒来
I like waking up with you too.
真是美丽的早晨
Oh! It's such a beautiful morning.
我可以在床上待一整天
Oh, I can stay here all day.
那样不错
That would be great!
我们可以在床上吃早餐
We could have breakfast in bed...
等等
Wait, just a second.
好
Okay.
见鬼
Oh no.
好啦  莫妮卡  精神点
All right! Come on Monica! Look alive! Come on, look alive!
很好  你们都起床了
Oh good, you're all up.
菲比  现在才早上六点
Phoebe! It's 6 o'clock in the morning!
你怎么没在盖瑞那里
Why aren't you at Gary's?
结束了
Oh yeah, that's over.
什么
What?!
别这样  盖瑞这么好
Come on! Gary's such a great guy!
有什么问题都能解决的
Whatever the problem is, you can work it out!
他开枪杀了一只鸟
He shot a bird!
结束了
Oh that is over!
-太糟糕了  -我很遗憾
- That's terrible! - I'm sorry!
菲比  你还好吧
Phoebe, are you okay?
我不会有事的
Yeah. Yeah, I'll be alright.
菲比  接住
Oh hey, here Pheebs.
我不太想玩球
Nah, I don't feel like playing.
没事  没事
It's okay. It's okay.
就当没发生这件事
Just pretend that it didn't happen! Okay?
没必要让别人知道
No one needs to know!
菲比又不是正式的队员
I mean, Phoebe's not an official ballplayer!
正式队员掉球才算数
I mean, only official ballplayers can drop the ball!
-算了  -我好饿
- All right. Okay. - I'm starving!
菲比  要吃早餐吗
Phoebe, honey, wanna get some breakfast?
好啊
Yeah!
我们来赛跑  最先到的赢
Okay! Okay, let's race! First one there wins!
你们要在这里吃吗
You guys wanna eat here?
好啊
Yeah!
想起来真的很棒吧
Man that was great! Huh?
真不敢相信我们丢了那么久
Can you believe how long we threw that ball around?
是啊  撑了那么久真的很不可思议
Yeah, it is amazing it lasted that long.
是啊  我的手臂酸死了
I know. My arm is killing me.
不  我是说有手滑大王在还能那么久
No, I meant with the dropper over here.
手滑大王这称号怎么会落到我头上的
Y'know, how did I get this reputation as a dropper?
我再怎么说也不是手滑大王
Okay? I'm anything but a dropper.
罗斯
Ross.